<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<jcr:root xmlns:dam="http://www.day.com/dam/1.0" xmlns:cq="http://www.day.com/jcr/cq/1.0" xmlns:jcr="http://www.jcp.org/jcr/1.0" xmlns:mix="http://www.jcp.org/jcr/mix/1.0" xmlns:nt="http://www.jcp.org/jcr/nt/1.0"
    jcr:isCheckedOut="{Boolean}true"
    jcr:mixinTypes="[mix:referenceable,mix:versionable]"
    jcr:primaryType="dam:Asset"
    jcr:uuid="7eb54bca-2a2c-43d7-b263-009fa617c5ba">
    <jcr:content
        cq:name="abu-dhabi-travel-guidelines"
        cq:parentPath="/content/dam/headless-shark/in/en/srp"
        jcr:lastModified="{Date}2023-01-10T11:53:07.359+05:30"
        jcr:lastModifiedBy="admin"
        jcr:primaryType="dam:AssetContent"
        jcr:title="Abu Dhabi Travel guidelines"
        contentFragment="{Boolean}true"
        lastFragmentSave="{Date}2023-01-10T11:53:07.359+05:30">
        <data
            cq:model="/conf/headless-shark/settings/dam/cfm/models/travel-guideline-popup"
            jcr:primaryType="nt:unstructured">
            <master
                jcr:mixinTypes="[cq:Taggable,dam:cfVariationNode]"
                jcr:primaryType="nt:unstructured"
                country="Abu Dhabi"
                country_x0040_LastModified="{Date}2023-01-10T11:53:07.340+05:30"
                importantTravelGuidelineDescription="&lt;p>For customers from India to Abu Dhabi&lt;/p>&#xa;&lt;p>Only the following categories of customers will be allowed entry to Abu Dhabi:&lt;/p>&#xa;&lt;ol>&#xa;&lt;li>Holders of all type of visa and/or entry permission granted by the appropriate authority in the United Arab Emirates with valid proof of WHO approved vaccination and generate QR code from the Federal Authority For Identity and Citizenship (&lt;a href=&quot;https://smartservices.ica.gov.ae/echannels/web/client/guest/index.html#/registerArrivals&quot;>https://smartservices.ica.gov.ae/echannels/web/client/guest/index.html#/registerArrivals&lt;/a>or register on the ICA Smart UAE APP (Click to download – Android &amp;amp; iOS versions of the ICA&amp;nbsp;Smart App)) (i.e., valid resident visa, employment visa, short stay/long stay visa, visit visa, residence visa newly issued from Abu Dhabi only).&lt;/li>&#xa;&lt;li>Holders of newly issued employment and resident visas issued from other emirates other than Abu Dhabi shall not be allowed&lt;/li>&#xa;&lt;/ol>&#xa;&lt;p>Visa on arrival facility is available for Indian Nationals travelling to Abu Dhabi provided they:&lt;/p>&#xa;&lt;ol>&#xa;&lt;li>have a visitor visa or a green card issued by the Unites States, or&lt;/li>&#xa;&lt;li>a residence visa issued by the United Kingdom or Europe union&lt;/li>&#xa;&lt;/ol>&#xa;&lt;p>Customers must carry a negative PCR certificate in printed form, from a government-approved laboratory in India (ICMR) or a certified&amp;nbsp;designated laboratory which is available on&amp;nbsp;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.icmr.gov.in/&quot;>https://www.icmr.gov.in/&lt;/a>issued no more than 48 hours before departure of the last direct flight to Abu Dhabi. The certificate issued shall be duly signed or stamped by relevant authorities and must only be in English or Arabic. Handwritten certificates shall not be permitted. 48Hours is calculated from the time of sample collection&lt;/p>&#xa;&lt;p>The negative PCR certificate held by the customer must have a QR code on it linking it to their original test report and must have the date and time of sample collection and the test result mentioned accurately. Customers holding a negative PCR certificate without a QR code shall be denied boarded at the origin station&lt;/p>&#xa;&lt;p>&lt;u>Note: Children under 12 years are exempted from pre-COVID test&lt;/u>&lt;/p>&#xa;&lt;p>Customers are also mandatorily required to undergo a rapid PCR test within 6 hours of departure at the airport&lt;/p>&#xa;&lt;p>Vaccinated customers shall not be required to undergo quarantine however will have to undergo a PCR test on arrival and on day 4 and day 8 or depending on their duration of stay&lt;/p>&#xa;&lt;p>Unvaccinated customers shall be subject to 12 day mandatory institutional or home quarantine as deemed fit by the authorities and undergo COVID‑19 PCR testing on arrival in Abu Dhabi. Customers shall also be required to wear tracking medical wristband&lt;/p>&#xa;&lt;p>All customers transiting Abu Dhabi, must carry a negative PCR certificate in printed form, from a government-approved laboratory in India (ICMR) or a certified&amp;nbsp;designated laboratory which is available on&amp;nbsp;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.icmr.gov.in/&quot;>https://www.icmr.gov.in/&lt;/a>issued no more than 72 hours before departure of the last direct flight to Abu Dhabi or less as per the requirements of the final destination. The certificate issued shall be duly signed or stamped by relevant authorities and must only be in English or Arabic. Handwritten certificates shall not be permitted. 72Hours is calculated from the time of sample collection.&lt;/p>&#xa;&lt;p>The negative PCR certificate held by the customer must have a QR code on it linking it to their original test report and must have the date and time of sample collection and the test result mentioned accurately. Customers holding a negative PCR certificate without a QR code shall be denied boarded at the origin station&lt;/p>&#xa;&lt;p>Vaccination only applies to customers who are aged 16 years and older&lt;/p>&#xa;&lt;p>All customers must download and register on the&amp;nbsp;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.weqaya.ae/en/application&quot;>ALHOSN App&lt;/a>&lt;/p>&#xa;&lt;p>All customers are also required to download the UAE Fast Track on their smart phones&lt;/p>&#xa;&lt;p>Click to download –&amp;nbsp;&lt;a href=&quot;https://play.google.com/store/apps/details?id=com.smartbio.idemia&amp;amp;hl=en&amp;amp;gl=US&quot;>Android&lt;/a>&amp;nbsp;&amp;amp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;a href=&quot;https://apps.apple.com/us/app/uae-fast-track/id1535632896&quot;>iOS&lt;/a>&amp;nbsp;versions of the UAE Fast Track app&lt;/p>&#xa;&lt;p>For customers from Abu Dhabi to India&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p>&#xa;&lt;ol>&#xa;&lt;li>Eligibility to travel to India: Stranded Indian nationals; All Overseas Citizens of India (OCI) cardholders holding UAE passports, and UAE nationals (including diplomats) holding valid visa issued by an Indian Mission in any category covered under Ministry of Home Affairs (MHA) guidelines dated 30.06.2020&lt;/li>&#xa;&lt;li>To know the detailed Indian guidelines for arrivals into India, please see ‘Arrivals into India’ section&lt;/li>&#xa;&lt;li>As per extant government regulations, customers are permitted to travel to India from the United Kingdom only on a direct flight. Customers shall not be allowed to travel to India through a transit airport of another country. Hence, all customers travelling from the United Kingdom to India via any other/ third country from where IndiGo operates its flight to India,&amp;nbsp;&lt;u>shall not be permitted to undertake travel on such IndiGo operated flight&lt;/u>. All liabilities, penalties, costs, losses arising out of such refusal of carriage by IndiGo or proposed travel, shall be borne solely by the customer&lt;/li>&#xa;&lt;/ol>&#xa;"
                importantTravelGuidelineDescription_x0040_ContentType="text/html"
                importantTravelGuidelineDescription_x0040_LastModified="{Date}2023-01-10T11:53:07.340+05:30"
                okButton="Ok"
                okButton_x0040_LastModified="{Date}2023-01-10T11:53:07.341+05:30"
                travelGuidelineSubTitle="Important travel guidelines for passengers to Abu Dhabi"
                travelGuidelineSubTitle_x0040_LastModified="{Date}2023-01-10T11:53:07.340+05:30"
                travelGuidelineTitle="Important information"
                travelGuidelineTitle_x0040_LastModified="{Date}2023-01-10T11:53:07.340+05:30"/>
        </data>
        <metadata
            jcr:mixinTypes="[cq:Taggable]"
            jcr:primaryType="nt:unstructured"/>
        <related jcr:primaryType="nt:unstructured"/>
    </jcr:content>
</jcr:root>
