<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<jcr:root xmlns:dam="http://www.day.com/dam/1.0" xmlns:cq="http://www.day.com/jcr/cq/1.0" xmlns:jcr="http://www.jcp.org/jcr/1.0" xmlns:mix="http://www.jcp.org/jcr/mix/1.0" xmlns:nt="http://www.jcp.org/jcr/nt/1.0"
    jcr:isCheckedOut="{Boolean}true"
    jcr:mixinTypes="[mix:referenceable,mix:versionable]"
    jcr:primaryType="dam:Asset"
    jcr:uuid="d7152caf-0258-43d2-a771-caae99773bfe">
    <jcr:content
        cq:name="dubai-travel-guidelines"
        cq:parentPath="/content/dam/headless-shark/in/en/srp"
        jcr:lastModified="{Date}2023-01-10T11:56:21.387+05:30"
        jcr:lastModifiedBy="admin"
        jcr:primaryType="dam:AssetContent"
        jcr:title="Dubai Travel Guidelines"
        contentFragment="{Boolean}true"
        lastFragmentSave="{Date}2023-01-10T11:56:21.387+05:30">
        <data
            cq:model="/conf/headless-shark/settings/dam/cfm/models/travel-guideline-popup"
            jcr:primaryType="nt:unstructured">
            <master
                jcr:mixinTypes="[cq:Taggable,dam:cfVariationNode]"
                jcr:primaryType="nt:unstructured"
                country="Dubai"
                country_x0040_LastModified="{Date}2023-01-10T11:56:01.553+05:30"
                importantTravelGuidelineDescription="&lt;ol>&#xa;&lt;li>The following categories of customers will be allowed to travel from India to Dubai:&lt;ol>&#xa;&lt;li>Holders of all type of visa and/or entry permission granted by the appropriate authority in the United Arab Emirates (i.e., valid resident visa, employment visa, short stay/long stay visa, visit visa, residence visa newly issued)&lt;/li>&#xa;&lt;/ol>&#xa;&lt;/li>&#xa;&lt;li>Visa on arrival facility is available for Indian Nationals travelling to Dubai provided they:&lt;ol>&#xa;&lt;li>have a visitor visa or a green card issued by the Unites States, or&lt;/li>&#xa;&lt;li>a residence visa issued by the United Kingdom or Europe union&lt;/li>&#xa;&lt;/ol>&#xa;&lt;/li>&#xa;&lt;li>Customers must carry a valid proof of vaccination which reflects the completion of doses of WHO approved vaccines or vaccines approved by The United Arab Emirates (UAE). The vaccine certificate held by the customer must have a QR code on it and should only be in English or Arabic&lt;/li>&#xa;&lt;/ol>&#xa;&lt;p>&lt;u>OR&lt;/u>&lt;/p>&#xa;&lt;ol>&#xa;&lt;li>Customers must carry a negative PCR certificate in printed form, from a government-approved laboratory in India (ICMR) or a certified&amp;nbsp;designated laboratory which is available on&amp;nbsp;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.icmr.gov.in/&quot;>https://www.icmr.gov.in/&lt;/a>issued no more than 48 hours before departure of the last direct flight to Dubai. The certificate issued shall be duly signed or stamped by relevant authorities and must only be in English or Arabic. Handwritten certificates shall not be permitted. 48Hours is calculated from the time of sample collection&lt;/li>&#xa;&lt;li>The negative PCR certificate held by the customer must have a QR code on it linking it to their original test report and must have the date and time of sample collection and the test result mentioned accurately. Customers holding a negative PCR certificate without a QR code shall be denied boarded at the origin station&lt;/li>&#xa;&lt;/ol>&#xa;&lt;p>&lt;u>Note: The following are exempted from pre-departure covid test&lt;/u>&lt;/p>&#xa;&lt;ul>&#xa;&lt;li>Children under the age of 12 years&lt;/li>&#xa;&lt;li>Customers escorting 1st&amp;nbsp;degree relatives of UAE national&lt;/li>&#xa;&lt;li>Domestic labour escorting a UAE national sponsor during travel&lt;/li>&#xa;&lt;li>UAE-Nationals&lt;/li>&#xa;&lt;/ul>&#xa;&lt;p>&lt;u>OR&lt;/u>&lt;/p>&#xa;&lt;ol>&#xa;&lt;li>Customers must carry a valid medical certificate issued by the relevant authorities that the passenger has recovered from Coronavirus SARS Cov-19 within a period of one (1) month (the date of recovery and the date of arrival). The certificate held by the customer must have a QR code on it and should only be in English or Arabic&lt;/li>&#xa;&lt;li>All customers transiting Dubai, are not required to carry a negative RT-PCR certificate unless mandated by their final-destination&lt;/li>&#xa;&lt;li>All customers&amp;nbsp;must download the COVID-19 Dubai Smart App and generate a QR code on their device before entering Dubai. Click to download –&amp;nbsp;&lt;a href=&quot;https://play.google.com/store/apps/details?id=ae.gov.dha.covid19&amp;amp;hl=en_IN&quot;>Android&lt;/a>&amp;nbsp;&amp;amp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;a href=&quot;https://apps.apple.com/ae/app/covid19-dxb-smart-app/id1504818399&quot;>iOS&lt;/a>&amp;nbsp;versions of the App&lt;/li>&#xa;&lt;li>All customers landing into Dubai shall be subject to random COVID-19 testing on arrival&lt;/li>&#xa;&lt;/ol>&#xa;&lt;p>For customers from Dubai to India&lt;/p>&#xa;&lt;ol>&#xa;&lt;li>To know the detailed Indian guidelines for arrivals into India, please see ‘Arrivals into India’ section&lt;/li>&#xa;&lt;/ol>&#xa;"
                importantTravelGuidelineDescription_x0040_ContentType="text/html"
                importantTravelGuidelineDescription_x0040_LastModified="{Date}2023-01-10T11:56:01.555+05:30"
                okButton="Ok"
                okButton_x0040_LastModified="{Date}2023-01-10T11:56:01.555+05:30"
                travelGuidelineSubTitle="For customers from India to Dubai"
                travelGuidelineSubTitle_x0040_LastModified="{Date}2023-01-10T11:56:01.554+05:30"
                travelGuidelineTitle="Important travel guidelines for passengers to Dubai"
                travelGuidelineTitle_x0040_LastModified="{Date}2023-01-10T11:56:01.553+05:30"/>
        </data>
        <metadata
            jcr:mixinTypes="[cq:Taggable]"
            jcr:primaryType="nt:unstructured"/>
        <related jcr:primaryType="nt:unstructured"/>
    </jcr:content>
</jcr:root>
